Guide to the Molka Reich papers, 1904-1986
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections & Archives
Molka Reich papers
1904-1986
C0229
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections & Archives
6.0 linear feet (9 boxes)
The Molka Reich papers includes playscripts, programs, puppetry newsletters, newspaper clippings, photographs, and scrapbooks with most of it dating from the 1930s to the 1950s. About half of the material directly relates to the Federal Theatre Project, especially the newspaper clippings, programs, and scrapbooks. Many of the puppetry newsletters and playscripts are from after the 1930s. Some of the material relates to the actor Scott Griffin who acted with the Federal Theatre Project in Miami, Florida, alongside Reich.
Reich, Molka
Related Material
Special Collections and Archives also holds the, the, the, as well as numerous other personal papers.
Biographical note
Molka Reich studied puppetry under Remo Bufano in New York during the 1920s. She and her husband moved to Miami, Florida, in 1930. While there, she joined the Federal Writers Project, and then the Federal Theatre Project. She started with the FTP as an actress but soon was working with the marionette unit where she made puppets, wrote and adapted scripts, and built sets. As an actress she appeared in the Federal Theatre production Engaged that was performed in August of 1936. She stayed with the Federal Theatre Project until 1939, after which she continued to be a proponent for puppetry. In Miami, she served as president of the Business and Professional Women's Club.
Arrangement
Series 1: Essays, newsletters, published works, and miscellany, 1904-1950 (Boxes 1-2, 9)
Series 2: Newspaper clippings, 1936-1986 (Box 2)
Series 3: Photographs, circa 1930s-1940s (Boxes 2, 9)
Series 4: Playscripts, 1920s-1953 (Boxes 2-6)
Series 5: Programs, 1928-1950s (Boxes 6-7)
Series 6: Scrapbooks, 1920s-1950s (Boxes 7-8)
Scope and Content
The Molka Reich papers includes playscripts, programs, puppetry newsletters, newspaper clippings, photographs, and scrapbooks with most of it dating from the 1930s to the 1950s. About half of the material directly relates to the Federal Theatre project, especially the newspaper clippings, programs, and scrapbooks. Many of the puppetry newsletters and playscripts are from after the 1930s. Some of the material relates to the actor Scott Griffin who acted with the Federal Theatre Project in Miami, Florida, alongside Reich.
Series 1 contains many different types of materials including essays, puppetry newsletters, play synopses, published plays, vaudeville sketches, marionette patterns in various sizes, and original artwork by Ken Bare. Materials are arranged alphabetically.
Series 2 contains newspaper clippings from Miami, Florida, newspapers. Many of the newsclippings are reviews for plays that Molka Reich or Scott Griffin were involved in. This series is arranged alphabetically.
Series 3 contains photographs both black and white and color and in a variety of sizes. Photographs consist of portraits of Molka Reich, and Scott Griffin, as well as production photographs, and photographs of a Jack and the Beanstalk marionette. This series is arranged alphabetically.
Series 4 is the largest series and contains scripts for plays and some radio productions. Some of the scripts have accompanying music, mostly handwritten. This series is arranged alphabetically by title.
Series 5 contains programs for Federal Theatre productions and non Federal Theatre productions that were performed in Miami and Jacksonville, Florida; Atlanta, Georgia; Long Island and Pawling, New York; and The Smithsonian in Washington D.C. This series is arranged alphabetically.
Series 6 contains scrapbooks that have been disassembled and foldered. The Molka Reich scrapbook 1928-1948 contains mostly material relating to Scott Griffin. There is also a scrapbook for marionette newspaper and magazine clippings, a scrapbook with clippings and programs from productions in Miami, and a scrapbook containing calendar programs for the Starlight Theater in Pawling, New York. This series is arranged by size of material.
Alternative Form Available
There are scripts from this collection and other FTP collections online in the.
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Donated by Molka Reich in 1980 and 1981. Scott Griffin material presented by Molka Reich for the Scott Griffin estate on June 25, 1979.
Index Terms
Corporate Names:
Federal Theatre Project (U.S.)
Subjects:
New Deal, 1933-1939.; Theater--United States.
Contents List
- Series 1: Essays, newsletters, published works, and miscellany, 1904-1980s
  Series 1 contains many different types of materials including essays, puppetry newsletters, play synopses and published plays and vaudeville sketches, marionette patterns in various sizes, and original artwork by Ken Bare. Materials are arranged alphabetically.
  - A & B Booksellers theatre catalog, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bare, Ken, 1930s (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Blueprint for portable stage
  - Bare, Ken, 1930s (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Original artwork for set and other designs - watercolors, pencil drawings
  - Denison's Vaudeville Sketches, 1904-1934 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Dolls and puppets, 1930s-1940s (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Newsletters, catalogs, pamphlets related to dolls, marionettes, and puppets
  - Fairy Tales for Workers Children, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Federal Theatre Project at George Mason University, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Pamphlets and newsletters related to George Mason events revolving around puppetry and the Federal Theatre Project
  - History of the Drama 20th century, circa 1935-1939 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - History of the Drama series, outline for class study, 1937-1939 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Letter, March 3, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    "Dear Charlotte", possibly from Scott Griffin
  - Marionette pattern for a 18" cloth marionette, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Marionette pattern for a 15" marionette, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Marionette pattern for a 9" marionette, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Marionette patterns for larger marionettes, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Marionette patterns (oversize), circa 1930s (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters, 1980s (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Newsletters from The Puppetry Guild of Greater New York, The Puppeteers of America, The Puppeteers of America Regional Reporter for the Southeast Region, D. C. Puppetimes, George Mason University Golden Anniversary Puppetry Festival, The Puppet Guild of Greater Miami, Barry University Department of Theatre, The Puppet Masters calendar featuring famous puppeteers, itinerary for trip to Japan (UNIMA XV 1988)
  - Notes on the Soviet Theatre, February 1946 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Play synopses (article from magazine?), circa 1920s (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Published plays, 1918; 1935 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    12 Plays for Boys and Girls edited by Ben Blake with pictures by Bill Siegel; The Slave with Two Faces by Mary Carolyn Davies
  - Shakespeare: Actor and Critic by George Henry Lewes, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Theatre Workshop, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Three issues: Art of Acting Issue (1936), Second Art of Acting Issue (1937), Fall Issue (1937)
- Series 2: Newspaper clippings, 1936-1986
  Series 2 contains newspaper clippings from Miami, Florida newspapers. Many of the newsclippings are reviews for plays that Molka Reich or Scott Griffin were involved in. This series is arranged alphabetically.
  - Newsclippings, 1981-1987 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - A, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Ah, Wilderness; Altars of Steel
  - B, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Boy Meets Girl; The Bride the Sun Shines On
  - C, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Candle Light; Chalk Dust; Coquette; Criminal at Large
  - Engaged, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Gallows Gate, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - If Ye Break Faith, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - M, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Miami Federal Theatre; Molka Reich; Mystery of the Boardwalk Asylum
  - N, September 25, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    "New Director Named for Theatre Project", article about Dorothea Lynch becoming state director for the Federal Theatre.
  - One More Spring, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Room Service, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - S, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Smilin' Through; actor Scott Griffin
  - Twelfth Night, March 31, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Two years of WPA, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - UNIMA (l'Union Internationale de la Marionette) Congress and World Puppetry Festival, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - When Knighthood was in Flower, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - You and I, July 1936 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Series 3: Photographs, circa 1930s-1980s
  Series 3 contains photographs both black and white and color and in a variety of sizes. Photographs consist of portraits of Molka Reich, and Scott Griffin, as well as production photographs, and photographs of the Jack and the Beanstalk marionette. This series is arranged alphabetically.
  - Engaged, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    1 production photograph featuring actors on stage. An actor in center is holding a gun to his head.
  - Jack and the Beanstalk, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Color photographs of Jack and the beanstalk puppet.
  - Molka Reich portraits, circa 1920s-1930s (Box 9, Folder 1)
    12 oversize photographs, 10 of which are professional portraits taken by Charles Cooper in Miami, Florida.
  - Molka Reich portraits, circa 1920s-1930s (Box 9)
    2 oversize matted photographic portraits of Molka Reich.
  - Molka Reich puppet demonstration, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 2, Folder 23)
    14 color photographs of Reich leading a marionette demonstration.
  - Molka Reich with Bimbo, circa 1930s; circa 1980s (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Portraits of Scott Griffin, Molka Reich, and an unidentified woman, circa 1930s (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Puppets and stage productions, circa 1930s (Box 2, Folder 26)
    9 black and white photographs of Reich's marionettes, staged productions with actors, and includes two photographs of an audience of children watching Bimbo perform.
- Series 4: Playscripts, 1920s-1953
  Series 4 is the largest series and contains scripts for plays and some radio productions. Some of the scripts have accompanying music, mostly handwritten. This series is arranged alphabetically by title.
  - Ambassador's Conference, circa 1930s (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - An Apple for Venus, circa 1930s (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Anna Christie, circa 1930s (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Another Language, circa 1930s (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Anteroom, circa 1930s (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Anything Could Happen, circa 1930s (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Art - Where Art Thou?, circa 1930s (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - The Baxters:The Baxters adopt a family, episode 24 by Ruth Moore, circa 1940s (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Beachhead on the Campus by Milton Geiger, October 1, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Before and After by Edward Mann, circa 1930s (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - The Blase Mrs. Dade by Carl Glick, circa 1920s (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Blockhead Hans photocopy, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Blood and Hoe Cake photocopy, circa 1940s (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Blow East, Blow West, circa 1930s (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Bruin's Inn by Ann Townsend, circa 1930s (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Caesar Gets Crowned, circa 1930s (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Celebration for Lincoln's Birthday, circa 1930s (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Cinderella, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Includes script and sheet music
  - Community Players, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - The Conflict, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Cousin Billy at the Circus, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Abstract
  - The Case of the Empty Purse by Sol Barzman and Mel Waters, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Dick Martin, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Scott Griffin's copy
  - The Economist by Ben and Sol Barzman, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - El Cristo, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Emblem of Guatemala, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Exiles, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - The Face, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Faith of a Child, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - The Farce of Master Pierre Patelin, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Farewell Appearance, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Photocopy
  - Felicia and the Pot of Pinks (children's story), undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Fido the Clown, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - The Flattering Word, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Flood Control, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Food, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Freud, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - The Frog Prince (for marionettes), undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Fumed Oak by Noel Coward; Bury the Dead, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Fumed Oak by Noel Coward, undated
  - The Game, circa 1930s (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Gas, circa 1930s-1940s (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Ghosts, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Ghosts (act 2), undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - The Glittering Gate, circa 1930s (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Good Night, Caroline, circa 1930s (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - The Greatest of These, undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
    Director's copy
  - Hansel and Gretel, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Henny Penny, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - From the Henry Morgan Show, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Includes note from Syl to Helen: "Couldn't find the columns I mentioned to you, but in the search uncovered some old Morgan scripts I did for the Eversharp show. The enclosed is an excerpt, from about the only one that could be cut and still be effective. Probably would serve as a space filler and be good for a few laughs. Will try to find the other stuff for a later issue."
  - The Hiccuping Mr. Higgins, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - His Majesty the Microbe, circa 1935-1939 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Photocopy of Federal Theatre Project script
  - Holiday, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - How to Tell a True Princess, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - A Husband for Breakfast, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - I Have No Prayer by Arch Oboler for the National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - If This Be Reason by members of the local #20, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - The Investigators, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - The Investigators, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Sheet music
  - The Irksome Beelzy, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - J. P. Dropabomb by Amos Hull, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Jack and the Beanstalk, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Jergens Journal, February 11, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Radio production with Andrew Jergens
  - Joe and Edna script, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - A Joke on the Sun (marionette play), 1934 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Kids Learn Fast, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Let Us Be Gay, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Liberty Skit, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Little Black Sambo, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Little Black Sambo, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Little Black Sambo, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
    Photocopy of script and sheet music
    - Little Black Sambo, undated
  - Little Red Riding Hood, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - The Londonderry Air; Where the Cross is Made by Eugene O'Neill, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - The Marrying Kind, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Memo to the People by Sol Panitz for the World Security Workshop, March 6, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - A Midsummer Night's Dream, undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Miss Marlow at Play, undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Miss Marlow at Play, undated
      Playscript; Theater--United States.
  - Miss Molbray's Big Moment, undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Music for World Brotherhood by Jerome Bayer, undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
    Script for the American Brotherhood: The National Conference of Christians and Jews
  - Nancy Hanks, Bondswoman, undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
    Photocopy. Includes four scripts, one for each actor.
    - Nancy Hanks, Bondswoman (Lemmer), undated
    - Nancy Hanks, Bondswoman (Sarah), undated
    - Nancy Hanks, Bondswoman (Tom), undated
    - Nancy Hanks, Bondswoman (Abraham), undated
  - The Nightingale, undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - North Flies South (radio play), undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - One Sunday Afternoon, undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Pan America's Reception Pageant, April 14, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Pageant on World Peace by Paul Harris, Jr., undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Peace in Our Time, circa 1939 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Peace plays: The Soldier's Dream, The Plow of Peace, The Little Green Table, circa 1930s (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Pierre Abelard, 1935 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Pinocchio, circa 1930s (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Pirates of Finance, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Play for Children, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - A Powerful Enemy, circa 1930s (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Princess Chooses, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Private Hicks, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - The Quest, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Recreation Project, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Multiple scripts with holiday themes
  - Red White and Blue Network (a satirical monologue), 1947 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Right About Face, untitled (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Recitation (an idea for an original radio program), undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Room for a Crib by Lee Gilbert, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Rumpelstiltskin, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Rust on the Iron Curtain by Abe Stone, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Saturday's Children by Maxwell Anderson, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - The Scarecrow Who Wished For the Moon, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Secrets, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Sham, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Sheet music and lyrics, circa 1930s (Box 5, Folder 23)
    Miscellaneous mostly handwritten pages of sheet music and lyrics, some for marionette productions
  - The Shepherdess and the Chimney Sweep, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Sixth Column, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Sleeping Beauty, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
    Script and sheet music
  - So You Won't Talk?, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Somebody - Nothing, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - The Soldier Who Became a Great Dane, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Snow White and Rose Red, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - The Stronger Woman, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Suppressed Desires, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Talk in Darkness, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Tarzan, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - The Tender Elves, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - There's Always Juliet, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - This is Heaven, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - This Thing Called Love, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Thorn in the Flesh, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Three Clever People, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Three Clever People, undated
  - The Three Little Pigs (a marionette play), undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Includes script and music
  - The Three Wishes, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Three's a Crowd, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - The Tinderbox, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - The Tinderbox, undated
  - Tinsel, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Tolstoy (essay), undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - The Totem, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Treasure Island, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Two Birds with One Stone, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Two Birds with One Stone, undated
  - Unknown script, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
    Pages 2 to 30. Characters include Mrs. Giles, Mrs. Adams, Harry, Miss Mobray, and Walter.
  - The Valiant, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - The Valiant, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - What's in a Name?, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Why am I a Bachelor, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Why the Chimes Rang, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Wonder Town, undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - The Youngest, undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
    Scott Griffin's script
- Series 5: Programs, 1928-1950s
  Series 5 contains programs for Federal Theatre productions and non Federal Theatre productions that were performed in Miami and Jacksonville, Florida; Atlanta, Georgia; Long Island and Pawling, New York; and The Smithsonian in Washington D.C. This series is arranged alphabetically.
  - A-F, 1936-1982 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    Altars of Steel; Ah, Wilderness!; The Bishop Misbehaves; The Bride the Sun Shines On; Criminal at Large; Coquette; Chalk Dust; Craig's Wife; A Classic Vaudeville; The Emperor's New Clothes; Engaged; Folk Music in the Roosevelt White House (produced by the Smithsonian Institution Office of Folklife programs)
  - G, 1930s-1957 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    The Ghost Train; The Gallows Gate; The Great Sebastians
  - H-L, 1931-1958 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    The Happiest Millionaire; If Ye Break Faith; Inherit the Wind; International Society for Contemporary Music; Lightnin (invitation and program); The Loud Red Patrick
  - The Marionette Unit, circa 1938-1939 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Double sided one page flyer for the Marionette Unit directed by Molka Reich. The front page features reviews from places the troop performed, the back features their repertoire.
  - M-P, 1936-1958 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    May Day; Margin for Error; The Mask and the Face; Mehitable Wing; The Matchmaker; The New York Idea; The 9th Guest; No Time for Sergeants; One More Spring; An Evening of Experimental One Act Plays; Post Road
  - The Molka Reich Studio, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Two invitations for events at the Molka Reich Studio.
  - R-W, 1936-1958 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    The Starlight Theatre (1957 Summer calendar); Room Service; The Reluctant Debutante; Smilin' Through (includes ticket, programs, press release, for Jacksonville, Florida production); Separate Tables; Sabrina Fair; Twelfth Night; Visit to a Small Planet; Whom Dreams Possess; What a Life; What a Woman Wants; Witness for Prosecution
  - Their Annual Minstrel Show (Miami Business of Professional Women's Club), April 1937 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Turnabout Theatre presents a repertory of puppet musical comedies and intimate revues, circa 1952 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - The Winter's Tale, March 1939 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Series 6: Scrapbooks, 1920s-1950s
  Series 6 contains scrapbooks that have been disassembled and foldered. The Molka Reich scrapbook 1928-1948 contains mostly material relating to Scott Griffin. There is also a scrapbook for marionette newspaper and magazine clippings, a scrapbook with clippings and programs from productions in Miami, and a scrapbook containing calendar programs for the Starlight Theater in Pawling, New York. This series is arranged by size of material.
  - Scrapbook pages, circa 1930s (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Separated 8.25"x9.25" scrapbook pages with 5"x7" black and white photographs adhered to them. Photographs feature marionettes and Molka Reich.
  - Molka Reich scrapbook 1928-1948 covers (Box 7, Folder 10)
    1 of 5
  - Molka Reich scrapbook 1928-1948 pages (Box 7, Folder 11)
    2 of 5. Newspaper clippings, programs, telegrams, and handwritten notes to and about Scott Griffin regarding theatre productions including: Coquette, This Thing Called Love, two one act plays performed at the Little Theatre (Bereguisse and The Torch-Bearers), a calendar for plays at the Florida Forum and Assembly (1934), The Pretender, Broken Dishes, Hired Husbands, The Nervous Wreck, The Big Pond, Why Wives Worry, Smilin' Thru, Thank You, and The Love Critic.
  - Molka Reich scrapbook 1928-1948 newsclippings, 1930s-1940s (Box 7, Folder 12)
    3 of 5
  - Molka Reich scrapbook 1928-1948 loose ephemera, 1930s (Box 7, Folder 13)
    4 of 5. Includes programs for The Last of Mrs. Cheney, Our Town, Little Women, and Room Service. Includes playscripts for If Ye Break Faith and Two Crooks and a Lady, as well as handwritten and typewritten notes, a flyer for the production of Coquette, and an entry ticket for the Manhattan Repertory Theatre Co. at the Miami Playhouse.
  - Molka Reich scrapbook 1928-1948 Billy Griffin (Box 7, Folder 14)
    5 of 5. Material relating to Billy Griffin (later Scott Griffin). Includes negatives and portrait print as well as report cards and calling cards.